
export const quizQuestions_3 = {
  questions: [
    {
      question: 'What is Array destructuring in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        'It involves breaking down an array into its individual elements.',
        'It creates a new array from the elements of an existing array.',
        'It converts an array into a string representation.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It involves breaking down an array into its individual elements.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which symbol is used for Array destructuring in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        '...',
        '{}',
        '[]',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '[]'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is Object destructuring in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        'It involves breaking down an object into its individual properties.',
        'It creates a new object by merging existing objects.',
        'It converts an object into a string representation.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It involves breaking down an object into its individual properties.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which symbol is used for Object destructuring in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        '{}',
        '[]',
        '...',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: '{}'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the rest operator (...) in Array destructuring?',
      choices: [
        'It spreads the remaining elements into a new array.',
        'It joins arrays together into a single array.',
        'It removes elements from an array.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It spreads the remaining elements into a new array.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What is the purpose of the spread operator (...) in Array manipulation?',
      choices: [
        'It merges multiple arrays into a single array.',
        'It splits an array into multiple smaller arrays.',
        'It removes elements from an array.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It merges multiple arrays into a single array.'
    },
    {
      question: 'How is the rest operator used in Array destructuring?',
      choices: [
        'By placing it before the array variable name.',
        'By placing it before specific elements in the array.',
        'By placing it after the array variable name.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'By placing it before the array variable name.'
    },
    {
      question: 'How is the spread operator used in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        'By placing it before an array or an iterable object.',
        'By placing it before an object.',
        'By placing it after an array variable name.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'By placing it before an array or an iterable object.'
    },
    {
      question: 'Which of the following statements is true about Object destructuring in JavaScript?',
      choices: [
        'It allows renaming object properties during destructuring.',
        'Object destructuring is not supported in JavaScript.',
        'It only works with arrays, not objects.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It allows renaming object properties during destructuring.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What does the spread operator (...) do when used with objects?',
      choices: [
        'It merges multiple objects into a single object.',
        'It converts objects into arrays.',
        'It removes properties from an object.',
        'None of the above'
      ],
      correctAnswer: 'It merges multiple objects into a single object.'
    },
  ]  
}